okay so now let's make a product so basically i have all of these images already prepared
um there's a checkout image maybe we won't do them all at once but hero thumbnail checkout
and then we'll do one two three four five i think there you need at least five gallery ones
okay could you please create for me this test product it is a bauhaus print jumpsuit and it
costs 230 dollars if you could please feature the listing if you could look at the pictures to help
me draft up the copy that would be great basically though it's just actual bauhaus prints that are
true to the style that were then printed onto what you would wear outside to go skiing basically
but it's hip and cool yeah check it out and then if you could draft that all for me and let me
know if i need anything else oh and i've got a new image here
attached a hero image, gallery, basically they're all labeled. Let me know if I need to give you
any more. So now it has two files that are uploaded. One of them is all about speaking in
the brand's voice. The other is everything about your products. And then it also has
instructions that basically tell it how to interact with you, and that's based on how it
needs to interact to be able to get information effectively to and from the website. So this is
the testing setup right now. So it'll say your URL right there once it's set up. And like I said
before, I'll just be giving it to you this way so that you can play around with it while it's on
the test site. Look at it on the actual test URL on the website. You can purchase one just like I
did in the other video. And then whenever you're ready, just let me know. And there's just literally
just one URL that I have to swap out in ChatGPT, and that sets it up so that it will be sending
new products that you could use. So that's it. Thank you for watching.
to the live website.